vwaudiforum.co.uk 2010-11-24

# VWAudi Forum - "Privacy Policy" - VW AUDI Forum - VWAF

| 

|  |  |  |  |   
---|---|---|---|---  
  
---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---  
  
|  |   
---|---|---  

**_\---- VWAudi Forum - The "Number 1" UK Community, Forum & News Source for All Volkswagen, Audi, Seat, Skoda, Bentley, Bugatti & Lamborghini Owners & Enthusiasts - VWAudi Forum ----_**

Welcome to **VW AUDI Forum - VWAF**. The Website & Forum dedicated to Volkswagen, Audi, Seat, Skoda, Bentley, Bugatti & Lamborghini

You are currently viewing our boards as a "Guest" which gives you very limited access to view the growing discussion forum and access our other features. By joining our **free** community you will have access to post topics, communicate privately with other members (PM), respond to polls, upload content, benefit from discounts, and access many other special features. Registration is fast, simple and absolutely free so please, [**join our community today**](http://www.vwaudiforum.co.uk/forum/register.php)! 

If you have any problems with the registration process or your account login, please use the "contact us" link at the bottom of the page, and a member of the team will assist you. **If you are a Company that wishes to advertise and participate on the site, please send an email to[Advertise & Support](mailto:advertise@vwaudiforum.co.uk) for more details.**

|  |   | VW AUDI Forum - VWAF > Forum Information > Forum Rules & Regulations Sponsored by In Car Handsfree  
---|---|---  
 **VWAudi Forum - "Privacy Policy"**  
| User Name |  | Remember Me?  
---|---|---  
Password |  |   
  
Notices  
---  
  
**Do you own a VAG related repair business? - Do you own a Company that offers components for VAG related vehicles? - Would you like to support & sponsor or advertise on one of the largest UK based VAG Group enthusiast sites? - If so, we would like to hear from you. We are always looking for top class Companies to join and support this website, so to get more details of our excellent value advertising packages please [ email](mailto:advertise@vwaudiforum.co.uk) for full details. __ **

**

**Please remember.... For the best selection of Companies offering services and advice to Members - Please visit the[Site Supporters - Directory Of Site Supporters](http://www.vwaudiforum.co.uk/forum/forumdisplay.php?f=215) for the latest Details - Remember - you support them - they support us... They are all there to help, and may even save you some money.... **

**

**

**\- Today's Sponsor - ******

 ** **

****

**  

**Forum Rules & Regulations Sponsored by In Car Handsfree** [ ](http://www.incarhandsfree.co.uk/index.php?main_page=index&cPath=340)

|  Thread Tools |  Display Modes  
---|---|---  

| 

**VWAudi Forum - "Privacy Policy"**

|   
---|---|---  
  
  # **1**  

24-04-2004, 08:45 PM   
  
---  
|  | 

stuart

\- Administrator -

|   | 

Join Date: Feb 2004

Location: Yorkshire

Posts: 5,392 

Thanks: 282

Thanked 260 Times in 127 Posts   
  
---|---|---|---  
  
**VWAudi Forum - "Privacy Policy"**

* * *

**PRIVACY POLICY**

This web site ("Web Site") is owned by VWAudi Forum ("VWAudi Forum" or "VWAF" "we" or "us"). VWAudi Forum respects the privacy of its users, and this Privacy Policy explains what information we collect on our Web Site and how we use such information. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. In addition, please review our Terms of Use, which governs your use of this Web Site. Your use of our Web Site indicates to us that you have read and accept our privacy practices, as outlined in this Privacy Policy. 

**This Privacy Policy Only Applies to This Web Site**

Please note that this Privacy Policy only applies to this Web Site. While on our Web Site, you may encounter links to other web sites or online material. If you "click" on a link to such a third party, the "click" takes you off our Web Site and to a third party’s web site, which is beyond VWAudi Forum’s control. These other web sites may set their own cookies, collect data, and/or have their own privacy policies. This Privacy Policy only covers information collected at this Web Site, and does not cover any information collected by any other Web Site or offline by VWAudi Forum (unless specifically stated), its affiliates or any other site, and we encourage you to review the privacy policy of any other web site you visit.

In addition, please note that this Privacy Policy does not apply to any information you may disclose publicly in any chat rooms, message boards, or similar web pages. You should keep in mind that whenever you publicly disclose information about yourself online – for example, via message boards or chat rooms – that information could be collected and used by people that you do not know. In addition, certain message boards and similar user forums may display IP addresses along with the message poster’s name and message. VWAudi Forum bears no responsibility for any action or policies of any third parties who collect any information users may disclose on the message boards, chat areas or other user forums, if any, on this Web Site. 

**Information VWAudi Forum Collects**

 **Personally Identifiable Information** : Generally, you may browse our Web Site without providing us with personally identifiable information about yourself, which is information that could reasonably be used to identify you personally (such as your name, address, birth date or e-mail address), which we refer to as "Details." However, there may be times when we ask you to provide us with certain Detail, such as when you choose to register with our Web Site and/or for newsletters. We may also ask you to provide us with demographic information or information regarding your interests, hobbies or similar information. VWAudi Forum reserves the right, at any time, to add features to our Web Site that require you to register or otherwise provide Detail, or to require registration to access our Web Site. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of or participate in many of the Web Site’s features. We may combine the information we collect with information available from other sources, including information received from promotional partners or other third parties.

We may provide you the opportunity to e-mail a friend an article, electronic greeting card or other special feature from our Web Site. The e-mail addresses you supply us for those activities will be used to send the requested e-mail and will not be used to send you or your friend any other e-mail communications.

This Web Site does not knowingly collect Details from children under thirteen (13) years of age: This is not a web site directed to children under the age of 13, and VWAudi Forum does not knowingly collect any information from children under 13 years of age at this Web Site. If you are under 13 years of age, do not send any information about yourself to VWAudi Forum. If VWAudi Forum discovers that a child under the age of 13 has provided this Web Site with Details, VWAudi Forum will delete that child’s Details from its system. 

**Anonymous Information** : When you visit this Web Site, our web servers automatically collect web site usage information. Web site usage information is anonymous information that describes how our visitors use and navigate our Web Site, and it includes the number and frequency of visitors to each web page and the length of their stays. We collect the anonymous information automatically sent to us by your web browser, such as browser type, referrer data that identifies the web page visited prior and subsequent to visiting our Web Site, and IP address. We also may determine what technology is available through your browser in order to serve you the most appropriate version of a web page. For example, we may determine that you have installed a version of Flash, and we will then send you the appropriate Flash version of the web page rather than an HTML page. 

**IP Addresses** : An IP address is a number that is assigned to your computer or network when you are on the Internet. When visitors request pages from our Web Site, our servers log the visitor’s IP address. We may collect IP addresses for a variety of internal purposes, such as system administration, to report aggregate information to our site partners or to audit the number of visits to different pages on our Web Site. Please note that some services within our Web Site, such as certain message boards, may display IP addresses along with the message poster’s name and message.

 **Cookies** : Cookies are information files that our Web Site may place on your computer to provide extended functionality and to personalize your experience at our Web Site. We may use cookies for a number of purposes. For example, we may use cookies to track usage patterns on the Web Site and we may use cookies when we conduct polls and sweepstakes to limit multiple responses and registrations. Or, we may use cookies to record registration and personalization information, enabling you to save your user name and password. We do not store any PII in cookies, but we may link the cookie to any information we collect. You can, of course, disable cookies on your computer by indicating this in the preferences or options menus in your browser. However, it is possible that some parts of the Web Site will not operate correctly if you disable cookies. You should consult with your browser’s provider/manufacturer if you have any questions regarding disabling cookies.

**VWAudi Forums Use and Disclosure of Collected Information**

VWAudi Forum: VWAudi Forum may use your Details to provide the information or content you have requested, to contact you about, features or services, or for other purposes disclosed at the time of collection. We may also use your Details to contact you regarding your use of our Web Site or changes to our Privacy Policy, Terms of Use or other policy or terms that affect you and your use of our Web Site. If you e-mail someone else an article, electronic greeting card or other special feature from our Web Site, we will use the information you provide about someone else to send that person the requested e-mail. VWAudi Forum may use information collected about our users to improve the content and navigation of our Web Site, or for other internal purposes.

VWAudi Forum does not rent, sell or otherwise disclose your Details to third parties unless disclosed to you at the time such information is collected or unless you otherwise give consent, other than in the following limited circumstances: 

**Legal action**. VWAudi Forum may disclose information about its users, including Details, when legally required to do so, at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our Web Site and applicable laws, or to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our Web Site. VWAudi Forum may also disclose user information whenever we believe disclosure is necessary to limit our legal liability, to protect or defend our rights or property or protect the safety, rights or property of our users. 

**Security**

VWAudi Forum takes steps to secure the data you submit to us, including limiting the number of people who have physical access to our user data. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Therefore, VWAudi Forum cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to VWAudi Forum and you do so at your own risk. 

**Acceptance**

By using this Web Site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. VWAudi Forum reserves the right to modify, alter or otherwise update this Privacy Policy at any time. We will post any changes here, so be sure to check back from time to time. However, we will only use the Details you provide to this Web Site in a manner consistent with this Privacy Policy, unless you give us your consent.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions, comments or concerns about our Privacy Policy, please contact us at [admin@vwaudiforum.co.uk](mailto:admin@vwaudiforum.co.uk)

This Privacy Policy was last updated on October 3rd 2010. © 2004 - 2010 VWAudi Forum. All rights reserved.

__________________

 **Stuart** l **_VWAudi Forum_**

 ** _VWAF - Administrator_**

**_\- Email:_** _ **[stuart@vwaudiforum.co.uk](mailto:stuart@vwaudiforum.co.uk)**_ \- 

_**If you need a Part, a Garage, a Tuning Company, or even an Official Dealer the please visit**_

_**our[Supporting Companies](http://www.vwaudiforum.co.uk/forum/forumdisplay.php?f=215) They are all there to **__**help by offering advice and products or services...**_

_**Details of the VWAudi Forum Insurance Scheme,[See Here](http://www.vwaudiforum.co.uk/forum/showthread.php?t=24937)**_

_**Take the "Skills for Life" challenge and become a better driver... Join the Institute of Advance Motorists**_

_**Fully Registered VCDS 10.6.0 - HEX-USB+CAN Interface**_

_**[www.vwaf.co.uk](http://www.vwaf.co.uk/)**_

* * *

_Last edited by stuart; 03-10-2010 at 03:31 PM.. _  

|  |   
---|---|---  
  
  # **2**  

23-10-2006, 08:22 PM   
  
---  
|  | 

stuart

\- Administrator -

|   | 

Join Date: Feb 2004

Location: Yorkshire

Posts: 5,392 

Thanks: 282

Thanked 260 Times in 127 Posts   
  
---|---|---|---  
  
**Additional Feature**

As of 23rd October 2007, the Website and Forum Administrator ( _Stuart_ ) has the ability to log into any members account with OR without the members permission.

This is to enable the forum administrator to take control of your account to diagnose any problems members may have with there account without you having to email your password.

This does not invade your privacy, or enable me to post on your behalf using your name.

__________________

 **Stuart** l **_VWAudi Forum_**

 ** _VWAF - Administrator_**

**_\- Email:_** _ **[stuart@vwaudiforum.co.uk](mailto:stuart@vwaudiforum.co.uk)**_ \- 

_**If you need a Part, a Garage, a Tuning Company, or even an Official Dealer the please visit**_

_**our[Supporting Companies](http://www.vwaudiforum.co.uk/forum/forumdisplay.php?f=215) They are all there to **__**help by offering advice and products or services...**_

_**Details of the VWAudi Forum Insurance Scheme,[See Here](http://www.vwaudiforum.co.uk/forum/showthread.php?t=24937)**_

_**Take the "Skills for Life" challenge and become a better driver... Join the Institute of Advance Motorists**_

_**Fully Registered VCDS 10.6.0 - HEX-USB+CAN Interface**_

_**[www.vwaf.co.uk](http://www.vwaf.co.uk/)**_

Bookmarks  
---  

**«** Previous Thread | Next Thread **»**

Thread Tools  
---  
  
Show Printable Version

Email this Page  
  
Display Modes  
  
**Linear Mode**

Switch to Hybrid Mode

Switch to Threaded Mode  

|  Posting Rules   
---  
  
You **may not** post new threads

You **may not** post replies

You **may not** post attachments

You **may not** edit your posts

* * *

BB code is **On**

Smilies are **On**

[[IMG]](https://web.archive.org/web/20101124141559id_/http%3A//www.vwaudiforum.co.uk/forum/misc.php?s=4e3078842f18e372b851dbb5a1d407e3&do=bbcode#imgcode) code is **On**

HTML code is **Off**

* * *

Forum Rules  
  
**Forum Jump**  

Similar Threads  
---  
Thread | Thread Starter | Forum | Replies | Last Post  
Greetings VWAudi Forum | Zipper | New Member Introductions - Sponsored by [BVR Automotive](http://www.bvrautomotive.co.uk/) | 4 | 27-02-2008 10:48 PM  
Hello VWAudi Forum | PendlePerforman | New Member Introductions - Sponsored by [BVR Automotive](http://www.bvrautomotive.co.uk/) | 6 | 21-10-2007 07:27 AM  
Hello VWAudi forum which had to go due to left ankle problems with clutch control in stop and go traffic, I am now a somewhat disgruntled owner of a 2002 Audi A4 Avant 2.5 TDi multitronic. The Passat only came with one key, bought...") | nicfw | New Member Introductions - Sponsored by [BVR Automotive](http://www.bvrautomotive.co.uk/) | 2 | 02-03-2007 10:07 AM  
VWAudi Forum - "Main Forum Rules" - Please read | stuart | Forum Rules & Regulations Sponsored by In Car Handsfree | 0 | 29-02-2004 09:08 PM  
  
All times are GMT +1. The time now is 03:15 PM.

| 

**Mark Forums Read | View Forum Leaders **  
  
---|---  
  
**-[Webmail](http://www.vwaudiforum.co.uk/webmail) \- [VW Audi Forum - VWAF](http://www.vwaudiforum.co.uk/) \- Archive \- [Privacy Statement](http://www.vwaudiforum.co.uk/forum/showthread.php?p=42#post42) \- Top\- **

Powered by vBulletin® Version 3.8.6  
Copyright ©2000 - 2010, Jelsoft Enterprises Ltd. 

\- Copyright ©VW Audi Forum (VWAF) 2004 - 2010 - 

**Disclaimer:** VWAudi Forum is an "independant enthusiast website", and is in no way related to any of the Worldwide Volkswagen,Audi,Seat,Skoda,Bentley,Bugatti,or Lamborghini group of Companies. For official upto date information on any of there vehicles, please visit the [official websites.](http://www.vwaudiforum.co.uk/forum/showthread.php?t=152) Any comments made throughout this website, are the views of the respective poster, and in no way represent the views of the VWAudi Forum Administration, or the worldwide Volkswagen & Audi Group of companies.

**VWAudi Forum do not vet and are not responsible for any information which is posted in this forum. All content is viewed and used by you at your own risk and we do not warrant the accuracy or reliability of any of the information.**

**Copyright:** Images used on this website by the Administration are "Copyright" of Volkswagen GB, Volkswagen AG (Germany), Audi GB, Audi AG (Germany), Volkswagen Motorsport GB, Volkswagen Motorsport AG (Germany), Audi Motorsport AG (Germany), Volkswagen Racing GB, Bentley, Bugatti, and Lamborghini. No image can be replicated by anyone WITHOUT the relevent Companies written permission.

All trademarks and copyrights remain property of their respective owners.

**No part of the VWAudi Forum website or forum may be reproduced without written permission from the site administration**

**PLEASE NOTE - PERSONAL ABUSE, ABUSE AGAINST THIS OR ANY OTHER WEBSITE OR ANY COMPANY WILL NOT BE TOLERATED. OFFENDERS WILL BE MODERATED OR EVEN BANNED.**

This website and forum are best viewed at a minimum resolution of 1024 by 768.

**\- VWAUDI Forum - The No1 VW Audi Forum - Volkswagen (VW) - Audi - Seat - Skoda - Bentley - Bugatti - Lamborghini - VWAudi Forum -**

**\- www.vwaudiforum.co.uk - www.vwaf.co.uk - www.vwaf.co.uk - www.vwaudiforum.co.uk -**

**-[info@vwaudiforum.co.uk](mailto:info@vwaudiforum.co.uk) -**
